



A UX/interaction designer by training, now a software engineer by trade, specialising in front end technologies. I love creating design systems that scale and accessible interfaces that delight - not just for the users that interact with them, but also for the designers that leverage them and the developers that deploy them.

## **Experience**

Software Development Consultant, Maltem Consulting Group; Singapore - May 2017 - Present

- Developed e-commerce applications, internal tools, libraries and design systems across the full stack of web technologies as a software engineer at AXA.
- Developed behaviour-driven development (BDD) automated testing frameworks and strategies for web applications as a QA engineer at SGX.
- Planned and participated in design sprints for both internal and other client projects as a UX Designer.
- Developed technical assessment strategies and interviewed potential candidates for new consultants.

UX Design Intern, Sonoport; Singapore - May 2016 - Jun 2016

- Worked with product design team to test application iterations through interviews and user testing.
- Processed test data to create actionable design insights that translated into real design decisions.
- Created style guidelines, UX flows and interactive prototypes to facilitate the design and development process.

UX Design/QA Intern, RetSKU; New York, USA - Aug 2014 - Jul 2015

- Worked with development team to design and develop dashboards in the main product offering of the platform's data visualisation.
- Designed and mocked up mobile application to facilitate efficient data collection for field agents.

## **Education**

**National University of Singapore** 

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) with Honours, Communications and New Media - Class of 2016

General Assembly; Singapore

Web Development Immersive - November 2016 - March 2017

## Skills

- Design/media assets: Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Sketch, Keynote, Ableton Live
- Front: React, Next.js, Sass, Vue, Web components, Gatsby, Hugo, three.js
- Back: **Node.js, Typescript**, Golang, Ruby
- Tooling: ESLint, Prettier, Parcel, Redux, Webpack, Styleguidist, Storybook
- Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, PouchDB
- Testing: Cypress, Jest, React Testing Library, Webdriver, Cucumber, Enzyme, Mocha